Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 7: Graphic Materials, 1977
  - Subseries 1: Color slides and negatives
    - Croatian Americans and Slavic Americans
      - Annuciata Church. Chicago, Illinois; Yugoslav Benevolent and Pleasure Club and Picnic Grove, Chicago, Illinois; Slovenian Cultural Center, Chicago, Illinois, May 27, 1977; June 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b47516; Richard March; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Serbian Americans, Norwegian Americans, Scandinavian Americans and Slavic Americans
      - Oplenac Yugoslav Folklore Group, Chicago, Illinois; Continental Night Club, Chicago, Illinois; J. Harry and Josefa Andersen, Chicago, Illinois, June 05 - June 06, 1977, June 05, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b47821; Carl Fleischhauer; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Polish Americans and Jews
      - Artworks created by Naomi Cohen, Chicago, Illinois; photographs, record labels, and memorabilia at the Sajewski Music Store, 1227 North Milwaukee Ave., Chicago, Illinois, June 07 - June 08, 1977, June 07, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b48693; Carl Fleischhauer; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Polish Americans, Slavic Americans and Ukrainian Americans
      - Balkan Music Store, Chicago, Illinois; Sajewski Music Store, Chicago, Illinois; Mrs. Maria Brama, Chicago, Illinois, June 08 - June 09, 1977, June 08, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b48700; Carl Fleischhauer; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - African Americans and German Americans
      - Mrs. Mary Belica's garden, Cicero, Illinois; Yaounde Olu, uniphysicist, at her Osum Studio, 2541 E. 75th St., Chicago, Illinois, June 10, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b48705; Jonas Dovydenas; 31 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Danish Americans and Ukrainian Americans
      - Bandurist Youth Group, Chicago, Illinois; Danish Singing Society; project photographer Jonas Dovydenas, Chicago, Illinois, June 09, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b48714; Carl Fleischhauer; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Hispanic Americans and Puerto Ricans
      - Sweet Sixteen party for unidentified Puerto Rican girl, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49875; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Sweet Sixteen party for unidentified Puerto Rican girl, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49881; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Rehearsal of El Conjunto de Cuerdas Típicas de Puerto Rico under the direction of Israel Maldonado at El Romance Club, 3575 W. Armitage, Chicago, Illinois, June 28, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b51723; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Mrs. Esperanza Sernas in her apartment, Chicago, Illinois; El Conjunto de Cuerdas Típicas de Puerto Rico at Channel 26's TV Studio, Chicago, Illinois; Jesús "Chuy" Negrete, Chicago, Illinois, June 24, 1977; June 27, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52860; Philip B. George; 32 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Slovak Americans and Czech Americans
      - Czechoslovak Society of America, Berwyn, Illinois, June 09, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49876; Richard March; 39 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Lithuanian Americans and Asian Americans
      - Lithuanian birbyne ensemble, Chicago, Illinois; Mr. Antanas Poskocimas, woodcarver, Chicago, Illinois; Street scenes of Chinatown, Chicago, Illinois, June 14, 1977; June 17, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49879; Jonas Dovydenas; 34 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Raising Lithuanian-style chapel pole, Chicago, Illinois; Buddhist Temple Street Fair, Racine and Leland Streets, Chicago, Illinois, July 02, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52021; Jonas Dovydenas; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Lithuanian Americans and Korean Americans
      - Home of Mr. Jae K. Lee; Sakadolskis-Pakstsa wedding at Immaculate Conception Church (Roman Catholic), 2745 W. 44th St., Brighton Park, Chicago, Illinois, June 24 - June 25, 1977, June 24, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b50896; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - East Indian Americans and Korean Americans
      - Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b51720; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Asian Americans, Hispanic Americans and Filipino Americans
      - Rehearsal of the Estudiantina de San Pio; Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, June 30, 1977 - July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b51722; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Lithuanian Americans and Hispanic Americans
      - Chicano Floricanto (Jesús, Rosa, and Bernardo Negrete; and Carlos Cumpian), Chicago, Illinois; Raising Lithuanian chapel pole, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977 - July 02, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52023; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Lithuanian knitting by Mrs. Stase Tallat-Kelpša, Chicago, Illinois; garden of Mr. and Mrs. Roberto Leval - Chicago, Illinois, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72638; Jonas Dovydenas; 17 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Slavic Americans and Hispanic Americans
      - Europe at Night nightclub, 2986 Elston, Chicago, Illinois; Los Amantes at El Romance Club, 3575 W. Armitage, Chicago, Illinois, July 05, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52028; Jonas Dovydenas; 24 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Lithuanian Americans and Swedish Americans
      - Swedish painting, Chicago, Illinois; home for Lithuanian American pensioners, Chicago, Illinois; Knights of Columbus picnic, Chicago, Illinois, July 04, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52031; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - African Americans and Hispanic Americans
      - Riddle's Bar, 312 E. 43rd, Chicago, Illinois; Latino soccer, Montrose Harbor Park, Chicago, Illinois, July 04, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52862; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Italian Americans and Croatian Americans
      - St. Rocco di Simbario Parade; St. Jerome Feast, Chicago, Illinois, August 14, 1977 - August 15, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b71992; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Croatian Americans and Indians of North America
      - St. Jerome's Annual Parish Festival; Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, Chicago, Illinois, August 15, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72635; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
    - Indians of North America and Korean Americans
      - Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center; Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist; Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72637; Jonas Dovydenas; 33 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-5, Lyman Pierce, executive director of the Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center, in front of American Indian Business Association Industrial Employment and Training Program office, 1124 W. Granville, Chicago; 6-10, Street scene, Davidson's Bakery; 11-13, Latino mural in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, depicting a rural scene presumably in Mexico; 14-15, Wall mural in the Little Village neighborhood, slogan on mural painted in Spanish ("El Respeto al Derecho Ajeno es La Paz) and English ("To Respect the Rights of Your Neighbor is Peace"), attributed on the mural to Benito Juarez, former president of Mexico; 16-22, Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush painter, with his work, 6244 N. Claremont, Chicago; 23-26, Mr. Park and unidentified children; 27-33, Mr. Park playing bamboo flute.